<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sample App M1</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="long_text"><![CDATA[TAG = MainActivity.this.getSimpleName(); baseline constraint   TO DESIGN LANDSCAPE ORIENTATION 1. Click the Orientation in Editor button Orientation in Editor button in the top toolbar. 2. Choose Create Landscape Variation.  TO DESIGN TABLET ORIENTATION 1. Click the Design tab (if not already selected) to show the design and blueprint panes. 2. Click the Orientation in Editor button Orientation in Editor button in the top toolbar. 3. Choose Create layout x-large Variation.  TO EXPAND 2 LAYOUTS HORIZONTALLY 1. Select the 1st layout {button_count Button} in the Component Tree, and Shift-select the 2nd {button_toast Button} so that both are selected. 2. Click the Pack button in the toolbar, and choose Expand Horizontally. to expand the layout to fill the parent horizontally  PLACES TO GET ANDROID HELP 1. Go to developer.android.com. This official Android developer documentation is kept current by Google. 2. Go to developer.android.com/design/. This site offers guidelines for designing the look and functionality of high-quality Android apps. 3. Go to material.io, which is a site about Material Design.  4. Go to developer.android.com/docs/ to find API information, reference documentation, tutorials, tool guides, and code samples. 5. Go to developer.android.com/distribute/ to find information about publishing an app on Google Play.   Google Samples Repo https://github.com/googlesamples http://officialandroid.blogspot.com/ https://www.youtube.com/user/androiddevelopers http://stackoverflow.com/help/searching  Installing DOCUMETNATION 1. …Click the SDK Tools tab. You can install additional SDK Tools that are not installed by default, as well as an offline version of the Android developer documentation. 2. Select the checkbox for \"Documentation for Android SDK\" if it is not already installed, and click Apply. 3. When the installation finishes, click Finish. 4. Navigate to the sdk directory you copied above, and open the docs directory. Find index.html and open it.  Sample App M1 Should Implement :  \tScrolling View \tIcon/Laucher config \tDifferentViews for Landscape & Portraits Views.]]></string>
</resources>