<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Article Title</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Article Subtitle</string>
    <string name="article_text">You can use the text in your text file,
        or use the text provided for the article_text string in the strings
        .xml file of the finished ScrollingText app. The only requirement for this task is that the text must be long enough so that it doesn\'t
        fit on the https://www.google.com screen.Keep in mind the following (refer to the figure below for an example):As you enter or paste text in the strings.xml file,
        the text lines don\'t wrap around to the next line—they extend beyond the right margin. This is the correct behavior—each new line of text starting
        at the left margin +2347033810120  represents an entire paragraph. If you want the text in strings.xml to be wrapped, you can press Return to enter hard line endings,
        or format the text first in a text editor with hard line endings. <b>You can use the text in your text file,</b> or use the text provided for the
        article_text string in the strings.xml file of the finished ScrollingText app. The only requirement for this task is that the text must be long enough
        so that it doesn\'t fit on the screen.Keep in mind the following (refer to the figure below for an example):As you enter or paste text in the strings.xml
        file, the text lines don\'t wrap around to the next line—they extend beyond the right margin. This is the correct behavior—each new line of text starting
        at the left margin represents an entire paragraph. If you want the text in strings.xml to be wrapped, you can press Return to enter hard line endings, or
        format the text first in a text editor with <i>hard line endings.</i> You can use the text in your text file, or use the text provided for the article_text
        string in the strings.xml file of the finished ScrollingText app. The only requirement for this task is that the text must be long enough so that it
        doesn\'t fit on the screen.Keep in mind the following (refer to the figure below for an example):As you enter or paste text in the strings.xml file, the text
        lines don\'t wrap around to the next line—they extend beyond the right margin. This is the correct behavior—each new line of text starting at the left
        margin represents an entire paragraph. If you want the text in strings.xml to be wrapped, you can press Return to enter hard line endings, or format the text
        first in a text editor with hard line endings. www.rockument.com You can use the text in your text file, or use the text provided for the article_text string
        in the strings.xml file of the finished ScrollingText app. The only requirement for this task is that the text must be long enough so that it doesn\'t fit on th
        e screen.Keep in mind the following (refer to the figure below for an example):As you enter or paste text in the strings.xml file, the text lines don\'t
        wrap around to the next line—they extend beyond the right margin. This is the correct behavior—each new line of text starting at the left margin represents
        an entire paragraph. If you want the text in strings.xml to be wrapped, you can press Return to enter hard line endings, or format the text first in a text
        editor with hard line endings. </string>
    <string name="add_comment">Add Comment</string>
</resources>